vapewild.com 2019-07-26

# VapeWild's Payment and Privacy Policies

**Payments**

VapeWild.com accepts Visa, MasterCard, Discover, and American Express. We do not accept Paypal or ApplePay at this time. If you would like to pay with PayPal or ApplePay, please contact them to voice your opinion about how you would like to spend your money. VapeWild reserves the right to cancel orders for any reason, resulting in the refund or void of associated payment transaction. VapeWild is not responsible for funds returned to a Gift Card that is no longer in the cardholder's possession. If using a Gift Card, we encourage you to maintain possession of that card until your order is received. 

An Order Status of "Awaiting Payment" or "Manual Verification Required" means that your order will be individually reviewed by our payment processing department. A few common scenarios that cause an order to require review are: the billing address does not match what your bank has on file, the billing address and shipping address are in different countries, or the billing address was entered incorrectly multiple times. 

Please allow up to 24 hours for this additional step.  It isn't necessary to let us know that your order needs a little extra attention - we will take care of you as quickly as we are able. Because we process these in the order in which they are received, contacting us will not expedite your payment.  We appreciate your patience!

**VapeWild, LLC Privacy Policy**

The website located at [www.VapeWild.com](about:blank) (“Site”), including all areas of the site, is operated by VapeWild, LLC, a Texas limited liability company (“VapeWild,” “we,” or “us”). We take your privacy very seriously. How we will handle information we learn about you depends upon what you do when using one of our services or Site (together, the “Services”). We strive to make our services as transparent as possible. We also hold the security of your personal information as our top priority. This policy will cover personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) and other information that may or may not be anonymous that you provide us through the use of our services or Site. This policy (“Privacy Policy) will explain what information is collected, how that information is used and/or shared, how the information is protected, and how you can control your privacy while using the Services. We reserve the right to make changes to this policy at any time and will update these terms on the Services when we do so.

**Information VapeWild Collects**

In administering the Services, VapeWild may collect from you, Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. Personal Information is information, that by its very nature, can be tracked back to you (“User”). Some examples of this type of information include your name, business name, address, phone number, email address, payment information and identification information. Non-Personal Information is information that is considered insufficient to be tracked back to the User (“Non-Personal Information”).

**Personal Information You Provide to VapeWild**

You may provide Personal Information including, but not limited to, your name, email address, date of birth, digits of your social security number, copies of state and federally issued identification, credentials, address, credit card details, username, and current location when you register and use the Services. 

**Information Automatically Collected by VapeWild**

Like other websites or apps, we also may collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate through our Services. We may collect information about your visit from the browser on your computer or mobile device including but not limited to the time and date you access the Services, your geographic location, IP address, device information, cookies and the pages you request — to analyze trends, administer the Services, track navigation of the site, deliver relevant advertisements and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use (note that IP addresses are not linked to “personally identifiable information”). We use this information to improve understanding of customer needs and provide relevant services. To automatically collect information, we use various technologies including:

Cookies. Cookies are small data files that a website you visit may save on your hard drive that usually includes an anonymous unique identifier. The cookie does not personally identify the User; it merely identiﬁes the computer with which the User accesses the Services. Unless a User voluntarily identiﬁes himself or herself (through registration, for example), the Services will not be able to ascertain the identity of the User, even if a cookie is assigned to a User’s computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information supplied by a User. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your e-mail address. The Services use cookies for User authentication, keeping track of your preferences, promotional campaigns that require User identification, keeping track of our audience size and traffic patterns, and in certain other cases. You can configure your browser to accept cookies, reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being used; however, if you do so it may render your computer unable to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other Users of the Services. Cookies allow us to provide better security on the Services, to customize the content, to track purchases, and to keep the Services working properly.

Analytics. We use various analytical services to better understand how Users interact with our Services. These analytical services provide non-personally identifiable data including but not limited to data on where visitors came from, what actions they took on our site and where visitors went when they left our site. 

**How We Use User Data**

We will use the information you provide to us for a variety of purposes, including but not limited to:

  * creating your VapeWild account

  * contacting you to fulfil orders placed through VapeWild

  * contacting you for customer service requests

  * contacting you to inform you of important changes or additions to our Services

  * sending you administrative notices, oﬀers and any other communications that we believe may be of interest to you

  * operate, improve and maintain our products and services, including analyzing User behavior 

  * administer promotions, provide features and display relevant content to you

  * track and monitor web traﬃc

  * track your response and behavior on the Services

  * interact with support and feedback platforms

  * manage support and contact requests

  * tailor and optimize advertising

  * to implement SPAM protection

**How We May Share User Information**

We do not give your Personal Information to any third-party services, except when it’s necessary to provide services (like when we partner with payment processors or other data services). When we share data with third-party services that support our delivery of the Services, we require that they protect your Personal Information to the same standards we do. We do reserve the right to disclose Personal Information when we believe that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with the law or law enforcement, to prevent fraud or abuse, or to protect our legal rights.

In accordance with federal and state age verification laws, we use a third-party age verification system, Veratad, to verify users are of legal age. We will collect your name, address, and credit card info, but may also ask for date of birth, last four digits of your social security number, and a copy of your state or federally issued photo-ID. This information shall be shared with Veratad. By using our Service, you agree to grant Veratad access to this information in order to allow Veratad to verify your age. Once your age is verified, all such data held by Veratad is stored for a period of up to 6 months and then archived.

Please see below for how we may share your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

When you send information to the Services, you are granting us permission to use and take other actions regarding such information, to provide the Services. We do not share, sell, rent or otherwise distribute this information to others, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. We may share your information with third parties outside of VapeWild under the following circumstances:

  1. With Your Consent: We may share information when you provide us with your consent to do so. This may occur when you consent aﬃrmatively or it may occur through your use of the Services as provided in this Privacy Policy. 

  2. Service Providers and Contractors: We reserve the right to disclose to service providers, contractors, or other third parties any or all of the information that we collect online about you and other visitors to conduct business on our behalf. These activities may include processing or making payments, maintaining the Site, or facilitating email delivery to you. We require that our service providers and contractors protect your Personal Information with the same standards we do but we are not responsible for their policies or practices.

  3. By Law or to Protect Rights: We may disclose information when we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, to enforce our intellectual property rights, to enforce our Terms of Service, or to protect the rights, property or safety of VapeWild and its employees, and if necessary to defend against third-party claims. We may also disclose information when requested to comply with a court order, investigation, or governmental request. 

  4. Business Transfers: If we go through a business transfer, such as consolidation, merger, restructuring, acquisition, or sale of part or all of our assets, you acknowledge and consent to the transfer of your information. You further acknowledge and consent to the continued use of your information by the recipient so long as they comply with this Privacy Policy.

Please bear in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your Personal Information available for viewing by third parties online, e.g. through comments and participation in forums or through email, that information can be seen, collected and used by others parties besides us. We cannot be held responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information.

**Sharing of Non-Personal Information and Aggregate Data**

VapeWild may share with third parties your Non-Personal Information and related aggregated data. Because this form of data does not identify particular Users, these third parties will not be able to contact you based solely on this data. For example, we may share aggregated usage data from our Users or may share IP addresses or general demographic information of our Users to provide anonymous aggregated data to business partners about the volume of use on the Services and the opportunities in which Users are most interested. 

**How We Protect All of Our Data**

VapeWild protects your payment information in line with Payment Card Industry (“PCI”) Data Security Standards (“PCI-DSS”), PIN Entry Device Standards (“PED”), and Payment Application- Data Security Standards (“PA-DSS”). As such VapeWild (a) observes, among other things, standards of due care with regard to the protection of sensitive Cardholder information; and (b) insures that the point of sale equipment and applicable software used by you comply with PCI-DSS guidelines. Currently, the PCI-DSS guidelines are based on a list of twelve basic security requirements with which all payment system constituents comply. VapeWild complies with these requirements, which are:

  * Installed and maintained firewall configurations to protect Cardholder data

  * Use of unique passwords and security parameters that are not default or vendor-supplied

  * Protection of stored Cardholder data

  * Encrypted transmissions of Cardholder data across open, public networks

  * Regularly used and updated anti-virus software

  * Developed and maintained secure systems and applications

  * Restricted access to Cardholder data by business need-to-know

  * Assigned unique ID to each person with computer access

  * Restricted physical access to Cardholder data

  * Tracked and monitored all access to network resources and Cardholder data

  * Regularly tested security systems and processes

  * Maintained policy that addresses information security

However, as eﬀective as the reasonable security measures we implement may be, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of a database, nor can we guarantee that information supplied will not be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet. Therefore, any information you transmit to us is sent at your own risk.

By using the Services or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Services. If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on the Services or sending an email to you. You may have a legal right to receive this notice in writing. 

**How You Can Control the Information We Collect, Use and Share**

If you share information with us, you will have the opportunity to review, update, or change the information you have provided to us (and that we continue to store) at any time through your profile settings. You can also stop receiving emails from us or disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account. Please contact us directly at help@vapewild.com to eﬀect changes or click on the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of marketing emails you may receive from us.

On request, we will give you a copy of all the Personal Information about you that we hold. This information is subject to a fee not exceeding the prescribed fee amount permitted by law.

We may retain certain information as required by law or for necessary business purposes. We are under no obligation to store such Personal Information indefinitely and disclaim any liability arising out of, or related to, the destruction of such Personal Information. In addition, you should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases without some residual data because of backups and other reasons. We are under no obligation to destroy anonymized aggregate data.

Regardless of your choices regarding promotional communications and updates regarding content, we may send you administrative messages, service announcements, terms and conditions of your account, or other similar communications, without offering you the opportunity to opt out from receiving them.

**Links**

The Services may contain links to other sites or services. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or other practices employed by websites linked to, or from, our website nor the information or content contained therein. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our Services.

**Our Policy Toward Children**

The Services are directed only at individuals of an age eligible to use our products in the state or country of their residence. We will not knowingly maintain personally identiﬁable information from or about anyone below the age of 13. If we become aware that we have collected personally identiﬁable information from a User of the Services that is under that age, then we will remove that Personal Information from our ﬁles. If a parent or guardian learns his or her child has provided us with Personal Information, he or she should contact us at help@vapewild.com (please include the child’s name, address, and e-mail address). 

**Consent to Transfer**

Our computer systems for the Services are currently governed and operated in the United States, so your personal data will be processed by us in the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. VapeWild makes no representation that the Services is governed by or operated in accordance with the laws of any other nation. If you are a visitor from outside the United States, by using the Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy and you consent to the transfer of all such information to the United States, which may not offer an equivalent level of protection of that required in the European Union or other countries, and to the processing of that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

VapeWild reserves the right to store this information in and outside of the United States and in locations not under our direct control (for example, colocation data facilities). 

**Changes and Updates**

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. To ensure that you are familiar with our most updated policies and practices, you should check the effective date indicated at the end of this Privacy Policy each time you use the Services. If we make any significant changes, we will notify you of such changes by posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Services. We may also send you an email alerting you of such changes. You will be bound by any such changes to the policy when you use the Services after those changes have been posted. If we make material revisions concerning practices where we have represented you, we will obtain your consent to use or disclose your Personal Information, and we will obtain your consent before taking any action inconsistent with those representations.

**Contact Us**

We welcome your feedback regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have questions, comments, or concerns about either one, please contact us by e-mail at help@vapewild.com

End. 

August 3, 2017
